谨以此片追忆逝去的童年，如果你也有这样的童年的话欢迎加入我们的贴吧"神剑传奇"。本作品之片源来自互联网，版权归原公司所有。任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途，一切后果由该组织或个人承担！制作者不承担任何法律及连带责任！请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
传司
F
xil le
传
F
2.∈
XI Ins
FRance 2. Etipse Animation, Tooncan Productions Xll Ine
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
校对：
pr oy
D
doMinique
Everything is ready
切准备就绪
a horse is waiting
for us on the beach
有匹马正在岸边等着我
WOlf, you're not going to
listen to this creature are you?
尔夫你不会真听这个小生物的吧
Herik needs me, Zek
哈里克需要我西克
For once in his lif
his father will be there for him
他的父亲头一次为他奔波
At least/ let me accompany you
至少让我陪你一起去
I go alon
我自己去就
I-don't want
to attract any attention
我不想引起任何注意
口回
You shouldn't pry into
the kingdom's business, Wolf
你不应该管闲哪的沃尔夫
You might regret it!
你会后悔的
第？集
Go black birds and
obey Prince Bragan's orders
去吧鸟兵听从布拉刚亲王的命令
Here
这里
Impressive!
真不错
ery good
you've trained them well
太好了你训练得很好
Bragan, my Griffins will
follow you to the little princess
布拉刚我的兽兵会跟你去对付小公主
and eliminate her once and for all
次性把她彻底消灭
Ah, brute force
啊野兽的力量
a tactic can
truly sink my teeth into!
项我能真正专心去实行的战术
What's going on?
What is he up
到底怎么回事他干么去
You've got to stay calm, Tara
得保持冷静塔
Maybe he met a patro
可能他碰上布拉刚的巡兵
He should be here by ' now
正常情况下他现在应该到
A
有人骑马过来了
here he
域在球
Ehere heis
他在那
Hey! Here we: are
”我们来了抱歉晚到
It's Wolf's fauilt
都是沃尔夫的错
He tsn't-quite as good with
norses as
with boats
也的术派没有他驾的技术好
平啡些欲影
sE sasot
slBoq liM
qIM poob se auinb 4, usy aH
He / isn't-quite as good with
arses as
with boats
也的术有地他驾服的技术卖
Where is my son Tara
我子在哪塔拉
He's with Queen Lorna
他和萝拉王后在一起
你是说我在后
orna
你是说萝拉王后
The queen is alive?
王后还活着吗
She was under an evil spell
她中了魔咒
Held prisoner inside.bod
被囚禁在莫西肚子里
She's free now
but has lost her memory
现在她自由了可失去了记忆
What does that, have to do with?
那该怎么办
Herik hasefound
a:way to cure her.
哈里克找到了治愈她的方法
but /e hawe to
getinto t
Palace
不过我们得进去王宫
That's Why we 'called for you
你来的原因航在此
loISJaAIP
w no
ou want a diversion
你想调虎离山
You want my/ men to risk
their lives for your queen
你们希望我的人为了你们的王后
冒生命风险啊
They don'thave
o stay and fight, Wolf
他们不必停留也不用动手沃
Just land on the
coast to lure Bragan
只需要登陆岸上
and his soldiers out of the palace
把布拉刚和他的人引出王宫
Uhk-ohl Weve got company!
了戡们疲跟
Uh-ohH We've got company!
疆了我们被了
Bragan!
是布拉
Oh, no
Oh. no!
噢不
He's got a gang
of Griffins with him!
他带了一队兽兵过来
Let's get themas far as
we can from-the royal= palace
我们把他啊引开离王宫越近越
et's get them asi far / as
we can from the royal- palace!
我们把他们引开离王宫越远越
Youawanted a diversion
r and now you,ve gotone
你们想调虎离山现在就是机会
auo 06 eA, no Mou pue
uoIsDeAip e palueM no人
You wanted a diversion
and now you've got one
你们想调虎离山现在就是机
We have to warn Herik
我们得通知哈里克
so he can get into
the palace in the meantime
这样他就可以马上进去王宫
Wip will takerof that
et's go
成售去跑号吧我们走
Wip will take
hat! Lets go!
威普去跑一趟吧我们走
、
/
Get themQuick=Go-on
抓住他们快点继续
L
Just a little moren your Majesty
再点里局吗
Concertrate!
熊中
No. ROad -.
么都想
NOm°oing
代么都想不起来
No. noone nothing
么都淑不
不不付么都想不糕来
NO no. nothing
不不什么都想不起来
Oho wby can't
噢为什么我什么都记不来
Your consciousness)
was almost completely wiped out
你被囚禁在莫西肚字里的时候
when you were hidden inside Mussi
你的意识差不多被完全消除了
But with the help of the Book
ife, I can restore your memory
不过有生命之书帮忙我能让你恢复记忆
Restore t'? How?
恢复记忆你准备怎么弄
Oh, this is all my fault
这都是我的错
Every person leaves a
psychic imprint herever they go
每个人都会在到之处留下精神烙印
sIf we find an object with
a strong imprint of the Queen
如果我们能找到一件王后
当时留下强烈印记的东西
we may be able
to restore her character
我们就可以让她恢复记忆
Understand?
明白吗
Herik! HerikHerik!
哈里克哈里克哈厘克
Bragan is after Djana and Tara
布拉刚在追捕裘娜和塔拉
Oh, and your father.
噢还有你父亲
Excellent! Thats
what we've been waiting for
太好了我们正等名呢
But, but .Bragan is
leading a pack of Griffins
队兽兵
Werve got to help them!
我们得去帮裘娜她们
Herik?
哈里克说话唧
We can't pass up the chance.
to get into Lorna's quarters
我们不能错失这个进入萝拉寝宫的机会
When her memory returns.
Bragan won't be a problem.
旦她恢复记测付布拉刚不是题
Theres a secret passage
那有个秘密通道
We Can use to get into the
palace without anyone seeing us
我们可以从那进去不被任何人发觉
是吗
Oh
Ive got a bad
feeling about this place
我对这个地方有种不详的感觉
he-Evil Forest!Terrific!
邪恶森林太可怕了
we go
Bragan is sure to follow us
我们要是进去布拉刚肯定会跟着进去
Exactly!
没错
And I know just the thing
to get rid of his black birds!
我知道要怎么摆脱那些兽兵了
If we must.
如果必须这么做的话
what's the quickest way
to the throne room, Mussi?
哪条路去大殿最快莫西
Mussi?
莫西你怎么了
Maybe she slost-her memory, too!
篇不好她也失
Ma. Mama?
后是后吗
Mama You've come back
母后你回来了
a
母后你怎么了
this my son
这是我王儿吗
This is terrible
这太糟糕了
Mamait's me Arthusl
Dont you recognize me
母后是我阿瑟斯
你认不出我了吗
I'll explain everything, sire
殿下我解释一切给你听
You mustn't worry your mother.
你不必担心你母后
Uncle Bragan was right
布拉刚王叔说得对
You are evil sorcerers
你们是邪恶的巫师
Help! Guards!
救命来人啊
You're making
a mistake! Come back!
你误会了回来
=
Make sure Bragan
doesn't-come back Wip!
威普去确认一下布拉刚有没有回宫
This way! Come with me!
这边跟我走
Guards! Guards
卫兵来人啊
It's the King
是国王陛下
Where is he?
下在哪
et's split ( up
我们分头扌
Erland boN watch dog, sentinel
监视
Ive really done it all!
我真的全他过了
Let's hope there's
stilla trace of you
希望那里有留下你的印记
Havea seat
请坐
No Bragan in sight
没有布拉刚的踪影
Don' t worry
别担心
Herik will have that
d queen fixed up in no time
哈里克很快就会把她变回原来的王后
PIl go watch the door
我去把
Shogi Master, help me
太法师请你郗
Only one?
-'II splitehim in two
我要把他劈成两半
two
I'll splits him in two!
我要把他劈成两半
My thought exactly!
正如我所想
think see what you mean
我想我明白你的意思了
Sorcery! I'll
never understand women!
巫术我永远也不会了解女人
句
It has its uses
这自有它的用处
For those who
know how to use it!
就要看如何利用它了
se
那么我懒
u
So
So I see
那么我懂了
Haven't we made
enough of these phantoms yet?
这些幻影够多了吧
Not quite!
还不够
There! I think that s enough!
他们来了我想差不多子
他们来我短差不
FeKr
e
Tara! Wolf! Now!
塔拉沃尔夫就趁现在
Theyre mad!
他们疯狂起来了
Let's go back and get Bragan!
我们返回去找布拉刚吧
And I thought-
sorcery was complicated
我还以为巫术多复杂呢
∠
气
Nol not them!
It's the humans I want
不对不是他们我想要抓的是那些人类
Brute force
野兽的蛮力
D
Then all of this is
nothing more than a diversion
难道所有这些安排还不及
个调虎离山计吗
These creatures of yours
are stubborn and stupid!
你的这些兽兵太难控制了又蠢得要命
The shogi is
in the palace, Bragan
布拉刚小术士现在在王宫里
've sensed his magic
我感觉到了他在施法
You- must return at once!
你必须马上回去
≈
Be gone!
快走
Out of my sight! All of you
滚离我的视线你们所有的笨蛋
A
一汉
Empty your rmind, Majesty
王后陛下请把你脑海里的东西排空
多
Herik. hurry!
hear someone- coming
哈里克快点有人来了
Please!
求你了
二
loo: I remember.
Yes!"Edwin, my lovel
我烟来了是的艾德温我的爱人
y
Fools
FOOls B
queeni
笨任率你样
后
Fools! By locating the queen
笨蛋你这样安置王后
have provided
me with the means
正好给我提供了个机
to turn her into my dearest servant
她变成我最乖的仆
Oh no! The sorcerer
不是那个巫师
Your memory is back, Majesty
你的记回来了王后陛下
It's coming from
the throne room! Quick
声音来自大快点过去
O
oh!
Oh
It's the queen!
是王后陛下
Lower your weapons!
武器收起来
Stand to attention in the/presence
een! Your Majesty!
站好向王后行礼后不
She knowsewho she is!
她知道她是谁了
You did it. Herikl You did
你成功了哈里克你成功
Queen Lorna
Youve regained your senses!
萝拉王后你恢复记忆了
Keep your distance Mussil
保特配离
Remember your place
记住自己的位置
You must act
quickly your Majesty
您得动作快点后陛
Bragan has allied himself
with the sorcerer. Kwodahn
布拉刚跟巫师科沃达同流合污
You've made a big
mistake coming here, -Shogi
你来这里可是大错特错
You will regret the
你会后
Lorna! Your Majesty!
萝拉王后陛下
You... you are alive
你还活着啊
Oh boy, now he's in trouble
好家伙现在他麻烦了
Uncle Bragan! Uncle Bragan
Mama has come: back
布拉刚王叔布拉刚王叔
母后回来
But there's something
with. her
可她好象有点不对劲
Prince Bragan
布拉刚亲王
want to thank you for
thaving taken caresof-the kingdom
我想对你表示感谢
and fmy son during my absence
多谢你在我不在的邀段日子里
帮我治理王国还照顾好王儿
and my son during my absence
多谢你在我不在的这段日子里
帮我台理王国还照顾好王
will now reassume the regency
我现在要收回摄政权
But I hope to be
able to rely on your couns
不过我希望能够继续得到你有效的建议
and your valuable assistance
和有力的援助
kI am your-humble
servant, your Majesty
王后陛下我是您恭顺的臣子
ama
母后
that really you, Mama
的是你吗母后
Stop whimpering. /Anthus
要喝阿瑟期
A true king /doesn't
behave like Such /a weakling
正的国王不会慧出如能儡的样子
Arthus!
阿瑟斯陛下
Now I think we're in trouble!
我想现在我们麻烦了
What is this Shogi doing here
个小术士来这干什
如 is an outlaw our Majest
王后陛示他个逃犯
and no doubt
intends to do you harm
而且毫无疑问他想加害于你
Wip, find Djana
and give her the Book
威普去找表娜把
生命之书交给她
Oh my oh my
啊
Stop him
Here we go agan
我们叉得出
Amd tell her what,'s happened
告诉她这里发生的事情
与
Notone of them followed us
他们没一个人跟士来
Guess they were too busy
al getting to know one another
我想他们忙得没时间去了解对方是谁了
Kwodahn's griffins
meet the ghost riders
科沃达的兽兵碰上鬼骑兵
Now that's something
I would have liked to see
现在我真想行看那精彩的画面
My son- standing safe
and sound in front of me.
我儿子安然无恙地站在我面前
That's something I want tosee
那是我希望看到的
Let's meet him
at the Royal Palace
我们去找王宫找他吧
Your mother
isn't herself, right now
刚才那不是王后她自己
but she'll be better soon
不过她很快会好起来的
Do you remember the song?
还记得那首童谣吗
t was your favourite
你最喜欢的那首
Lullaby and good night.
you're a mother's delight
快安睡小宝贝你是妈妈的开心果
Sleepyhead, close your eyes
睡吧闭上眼睛
Mothers right here beside you
妈妈就在这里陪着你
I protect you from harm
我会保护你让你远离伤害
You will wake in my arms
你会在我臂弯中醒来
Guardian angels are near
go to sleep with no fear
守护天使来了安然入睡
So, now Lorna knows who she
那么现在萝拉知道自己是谁了
but she's not
acting like herself
不过行为不象她自己
Somie thing went wrong, but what?
出问题了可是哪里出错了呢
Herik made a mistake the.time
哈里克一开始就错
t's not onsense
寺法术不是胡闹
It's the best way we have
to fight Kwodahn's magic
它是我们用来对付科沃达最好的方法
You can stay here and
cast all the spells you want
你呆在这里弄你想弄的什么法术吧
I'm going to rescure my son!
我去救我
It's the Great Wise Man!
是大法师
Evil leaves its
shadow wherever it goes
邪恶从暗处钻了出来无孔不
Evil leaves Ms
无不入
Evil leaves its
shadow wherever it goes
邪恶从暗处钻了出来无孔不入
It dims the mind and
soul of everyone it touches
接触过它的人都会被它蒙蔽心智
But it cannot
withstand the light of love
不过它终究抵挡不了爱之光
Love?
爱
More shogi nonsense
又是见鬼的三基寺法师
Now wOlf, he just told
me how to cure the Queen
不沃尔夫犬法师只是告诉我们
如何治愈王后
and get Herik back!
然后救回哈里克
But it depends on getting a
certain little boy to trust me
不过得想办法让小家伙相信我
Mussi, why has
Mother become so mean
莫西为什么母后变得这么刻薄啊
I think
because of the Demon.
我想应该是那个思魔搞的鬼
It appeared as the young Shogi was
bringing back your mother's memory.
在那个年轻法师帮你母后找回
记忆的时候那个恶魔出现过
If she doesnt go
back to her old self
如果她没有变回原来的母后
I'm leaving this place
我会离开这里
Come. come
Don't say such things
好了好了不要说这些了
Come to bed
休息吧
I'm sure there's a way to
rid her of that bad influence
我肯定会有办法让你母后摆脱那个恶魔的
We'll talk about it tomorrow
我们明天再讨论吧
平
Good night, little majest
晚安小陛下
MussileIt's me!
Wip, the dragon
莫西是我威普那条小龙
Princess Djana wants us
orto bring Arthus to her
裘娜公主想让我们把阿瑟斯陛下
at the village of Quinn
带去奎恩见她
What? You want me
to kidnap Arthus?
什么你们想让我绑架阿瑟斯陛下
Has everyone gone mad
大家是不是都疯了
You must trust Princess Djana
你得相信裘娜主
It's for the queens
own good .. and his
一这是为王后着想也是为阿斯
But couldn't
可我不能
Alright
端
Good work. Kwodahn
the queen is perfect
干得好科沃迟这个王后真不错
She'll be very useful to us
她会对我们非常有帮助的
We'l see about that
我们拭目以待吧
Djana has Arthus and
wants to swap him for Herik
,裘娜让人带走了阿瑟斯
她想用他来交换哈里克
Let's refuse
我们拒绝她
orna has become evil
萝拉已经是我们的人了
but being a mother. she will
still want to get her son back.
可作为母亲她还是会希望儿子回到身边
Too bad! Without her
Shogi, Djana is doomed
可惜没有小术士裘娜就完蛋了
It's only a question of time
这只是时间问题
Now that the queen is with us
现在王后在我们这边
we will soon possess xcalibur!
我们会很快拥有神剑了
Bat we must get: Arthus bac
不过我们必须把阿瑟斯换回来
They may try to use the boy
to rally the people to their sidel
他们可能会利用那个小鬼凝聚更多支持者
It's a trap isn' t it
这是个陷阱对吧
Of course it is
but it doesn' t matter
当然不过没关系
Did you get what I asked for?
我要的东西拿到了吗
二
Lorna's crown
萝拉的王冠
Yes, and as long
as she wears it
没错只要她戴上这个王冠
she will be under
my complete contro
她就完全受我控制了
As spain as Atas is safe
As sodAs An
safe
国闻瑟斯安全疗
As soon as rtus is, safe
As woolas Arthus
safe
贴全了
I want all the rebels
captured and executed
我希望你傅巴听有造反者抓起来处决掉
With pleasure, your Majesty
非常乐意效劳王后陛下
上
s An ambush! Don' t let
them get near the prisoner
有埋伏不要让他们靠近囚犯
多
声
An ambush! Don' t let
them get near the queen
有埋
要让他们靠近王后陛下
Fools! I'll take care of them
笨蛋我去对付他们
Let me go! Help, guards!
放开我救命来人啊
Let nfe" go
Let me go! Help, guards
放开我救命来人啊
Forget everyone else, Bragan
别指望别人帮忙布拉刚
Let's make this
between you and me!
我们两个来解决这个问题
I wouldn't haveit any other way
我也正有此意
Your reign is over
Bragan! Starting toda
布拉刚你的暴政结束了从今天开始
形
will have you
executed for this
我要以此罪名将你处死
Your Majesty, literally
hope can change your mind
陛下我真的希望能改变你的想法
I hate witchcraft
我讨厌巫术
That's Kwodahn's
magic. the worst kind
是科沃达的巫术最邪恶的那
Keep going
你们继续
Were almost there
我很快就过去
We've seen worsel
我们碰到过更恐训墓治锒园伤扛
Fighting s身
side, like the
肩并肩战斗象饺渐用样
I'd like nothing better
than to believe you olf
我想相
可我做不到
But -don't
So… you have sided
with your father's enemies.
如此说来你站到你父王的敌人那边去了
He would be ashamed of you
他会为你感到耻辱的
know that you arent my mother!
我知道现在你不是我母后本
Isn't that right?
对吗
Il bring you back
your mother. I promise
我会犯你母后找回来我保证
Relax. Arthus
放轻松阿瑟斯
Your tricks
't impress me. Sho
你的诡计影响不了我/
ove
places hate
Good erases evil
Oh no it's starting again
不又开始了
多
Herik
哈里克
Tara! Duck!
塔拉蹲下
Herik!
哈里克你怎么
s
E
a
Father
父亲
Herik.. my-son
里克我的儿子
You saved my life, Father.
你救了我父亲
Now I'll take care of you!
现在由我来照顾你
Dont bother to pretend Herik
不用白费力气了哈里
No! You're not going to die
不你不会死的
You'll fight
你会继续战斗
A Man of the Sea
never gives up, never
海每上枭雄从不言放弃从不
You taught me that
你教我的
i didn't have the chance
to teach you much, Herik,
我没有太多机会可以教你哈里克
but I'm prou
f you all the same
可我还是很为你
because you have couragea
因为你很勇敢
Be brave for me no
现在为我勇敢
my last sigh
be of my brave son
让我最后一眼记住我英勇的儿子
参
Father
父亲
-Mother.
母后你怎么了
You're not dead
you're just sleeping
你没死你只是睡着
Aren't you?
图度
Guardian angels are near
守护天使来了
go to sleep with no fear
安然入睡吧
Sleepyhead, close your eyes.
My baby!
睡吧闭上眼睛我的宝贝
Mama
母后
Princess Djana
裘娜公主
Your companions are
n our hands! Surrender
你的同伴在我们手上投降吧
sten to me
听我说
Prince Bragan-has disappeared
布拉刚亲王不见了
las run awa
他逃跑了
There' s no more point in fighting
没有动手的必要了吧
Of course, I don't expect you
to just take my word for it
当然我不指望你们会听我的话
Lower your weapons
and free your prisoners
放下武器把囚犯放
引e5
Yes, majesty!
遵命王后陛下
It is time to restore law
and justice in thek
ngdom
是时候恢复王国的法
题
Princ
Diana
表娜公主
Princess Djana
I will- await you in the palace
我在王宫等你
where youll be my guests
届时你将成为我的上宾
Im sure you
have much to tell me
严我肯定你有很多事情要跟我说
Come, Arthus
来吧阿瑟斯
were going home
我们回宫吧
世
E
Herik!
对了哈里克
Rest in peace, Wolf
安息
I'm.sorry, Herik
真遗憾哈里克
XUBEKTOR
ErECUTTYE STORY EDITOR
recuT
SCRIPT SUPERYISOR
scR
ureLs PEH OR
IEcUTTYE
EDITOR
SCKIVDE DNSNLTM
STORTOKRO RTISTS
erective SToK EDro
TuD属XNG
ElPS
PRODUCTION XOMINLTRKTOR- TOONCKN PRODUCTIONS IM INC.
STUDIO MTNKS
PRODUCTION ADMINISTRAT
LOT
PRODU
3D-MODELING
PRODUCTION ADMINST ATOK BoURDeau pRoductioNs h
H"5
IDMODELING
6kIBouILLeN
3D-MODELING
GRIBOUILLE
SRIBOUILLE
KOOUCTION
PRODUCTI
TSSISTIMT
G
oaReCTOK OP PHOTOGRKPMT
器器
)D.MODELN SUPERTtSORS
soe素
G ARTIS
DeveLoper
G AKTIT
CG AKTIS
rES热其
ARTIST
MOTION CAPTURE
SIUcoN STHDIO
C6C6 INC
翻译：英语辅导频道
输入/时间轴/压制：harry159821/黑月
校对：